<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jindu Kwentua</title>
    <link>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jindu Kwentua</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL MEDIA AND SENTIMENT ANALYSIS: THE PAST 2 NIGERIAN ELECTIONS</title>
      <link>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Twitter undoubtedly contains a diverse range of political insight and commentary. To what extent is this representative of an electorate? Can we analyze political sentiment effectively enough to capture the voting intentions of a nation during an election campaign? In this present day, social media platforms are playing a vital role in influencing people’s sentiment in favour or against a government or an organization. Twitter-based data is not inherently a representative sample of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis on COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>On 11th March 2020, World Health Organization announced COVID19 outbreak as a pandemic. Starting from China, this virus has infected and killed thousands of people from Italy, Spain, USA, Iran and other countries as well. While this pandemic has continued to affect the lives of millions, a number of countries have resorted to complete lockdown. During this lockdown, people have taken social networks to express their feelings and find a way to calm themselves down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science and Loan Applications. What can we learn about loans in Nigeria?</title>
      <link>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jindukwentua.github.io/my_portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>With the innovation in the banking/financial sector, people are applying for bank loans but the banks have its limited assets which it has to grant to limited people only, so finding out to whom loans can be granted to will be a safer option for the bank. In this project we try to reduce this risk factor behind selecting the safe person so as to save lots of bank efforts and assets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>